<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<profile name="global" version="0.20091110" standalone="no">
  <desc>
    The basic set of elements allowed for every object type.
  </desc>

  <field name="key" required="true">
    Uniquely identifies this item in the database. Identifiers must begin
    with the contributor namespace, followed by a '.' and then a unique string
    within that namespace which consists only of the following characters:
    A-Za-z0-9_:.-
  </field>

  <field name="id" multiValued="true">
    A local resource identifier.
  </field>

  <field name="pkey">
    The key field of the parent to which the object belongs.
  </field>

  <field name="gkey" multiValued="true">
    The key field of a container object for which this object is a group
    member. Groups are not bound by hierarchy, but should probably not be
    circular.
  </field>

  <field name="seq">
    An integer &gt;0 designating the relative position (sequence) of this
    object within its parent container. Numbers do not have to be
    contiguous (but should be when possible for efficiency).
  </field>

  <field name="type" required="true">
    The name of the application profile for this record.
  </field>

  <field name="contributor" required="true">
    The unique namespace established for the contributor, usually an ILL code if
    one exists. It must consist of A-Za-z0-9_.
  </field>
  
  <field name="label" required="true">
    A descriptive label (e.g. title) that can be used as the standard way
    to describe or refer to this item.
  </field>
  
  <field name="clabel" required="true">
    Like label, but used in the context of the parent item. For example,
    this could be a page number for a page record or a volume/issue number
    for an issue in a serial.
  </field>

  <field name="pubmin" required="true">
    The earliest publication year for this object. If the object
    describes a series of items, this should be the publication date of
    the earliest item. For items with uncertain dates, this is the lowest
    estimated date.
  </field>

  <field name="pubmax" required="true">
    The latest publication year for this object. See pubmin for more
    information.
  </field>

  <field name="lang" multiValued="true">
    Language of the content of this object. Should be a lower-case
    international language code (en, fr, etc.).
  </field>

  <field name="mtype" multiValued="true">
    Material type description. Should be taken from a controlled list,
    with values like "text," "audio," etc.
  </field>

  <field name="ctype" multiValued="type">
    Content type description. Should be taken from a controlled list, with
    values like "speech," "dictionary," "diary," etc.
  </field>
 
</profile>
